<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Groceries &#8211; Mật Gấu Thần Kỳ</title>
	<atom:link href="https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product-category/groceries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy</link>
	<description>Health is Wealth</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 02:42:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cropped-Icon-Mat-Gau-Than-Ky-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Groceries &#8211; Mật Gấu Thần Kỳ</title>
	<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Handpicked Red Chillies</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/handpicked-red-chillies/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/handpicked-red-chillies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 07:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/handpicked-red-chillies/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Red chillies can also be used to add flavor and heat to dishes, as well as being used to make sauces and marinades.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Red chillies are an important and popular ingredient in many cuisines around the world, but they can also be used for their various health benefits. Studies have suggested that consuming red chillies can help to boost the immune system, reduce inflammation and pain, and even lower blood pressure. Additionally, red chillies have been linked to improved metabolism, aiding in weight loss and reducing cholesterol levels. Moreover, red chillies contain high levels of antioxidants, which can help to protect cells from damage caused by free radicals. Red chillies can also be used to add flavor and heat to dishes, as well as being used to make sauces and marinades.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/handpicked-red-chillies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pulses From Organic Farm</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/pulses-from-organic-farm/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/pulses-from-organic-farm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 07:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/pulses-from-organic-farm/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Organic pulses are a great addition to any diet, providing high levels of protein, fiber, and minerals such as iron, magnesium, and zinc.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Organic pulses are a great addition to any diet, providing high levels of protein, fiber, and minerals such as iron, magnesium, and zinc. They are also rich in phytonutrients and antioxidants that can help protect against a variety of diseases. Additionally, organic pulses have a longer shelf life than conventional pulses, as they are not treated with preservatives or other additives.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/pulses-from-organic-farm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hand Sanitizer</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/hand-sanitizer/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/hand-sanitizer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 07:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/hand-sanitizer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Hand sanitizers can help reduce the risk of illness and the spread of bacteria and viruses.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Properly used, hand sanitizers can help reduce the risk of illness and the spread of bacteria and viruses. To use hand sanitizer effectively, it is important to apply the product to the hands and rub them together until they are dry. Hand sanitizers should not be used on visibly soiled hands, and it is important to follow the package directions for proper use.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/hand-sanitizer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fresh Organic Honey</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/fresh-organic-honey/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/fresh-organic-honey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/fresh-organic-honey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Fresh organic honey is a nutritious and delicious food that can be used in many recipes or enjoyed as a sweet spread on toast or other foods. </span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Fresh organic honey is a nutritious and delicious food that can be used in many recipes or enjoyed as a sweet spread on toast or other foods. Unlike normal honey, organic honey is produced from beehives in areas where there are less chemicals and pesticides in the environment. This type of honey is known for its distinct flavor and aroma, as well as its high nutritional value. It is known for having higher levels of antioxidants than conventional honey, and it is free of additives, preservatives, and other artificial ingredients. Organic honey is also more beneficial to bees, since it is derived from hives that are not treated with chemicals or pesticides. It is also seen as sustainable and environmentally friendly due to its lack of chemical treatments. Organic honey can be used in a wide range of cooking and baking recipes. It is often used as a natural sweetener for coffee, tea, and other beverages, and can be used as a topping for breakfast foods like pancakes or waffles. Additionally, it can be used in marinades and dressings, as well as desserts like ice cream or cakes.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/fresh-organic-honey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Natural Extracted Edible Oil</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/natural-extracted-olive-oil/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/natural-extracted-olive-oil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/natural-extracted-olive-oil/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}"> These oils are extracted from the source material through a cold-pressed process, which preserves flavor, color, and nutrient content.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Natural extracted edible oil refers to an oil that is produced from an organic source of seeds and nuts. These oils are extracted from the source material through a cold-pressed process, which preserves flavor, color, and nutrient content. Our natural extracted edible oils are free from additives or preservatives and contain a higher concentration of naturally occurring antioxidants. These oils can be used in cooking, baking, and as a dressing or marinade and are known to have numerous health benefits.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/natural-extracted-olive-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Assorted Coffee</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/assorted-coffee/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/assorted-coffee/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/assorted-coffee/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Assorted coffee includes a variety of blends, roasts and flavors. Each type of coffee beverage is made with different coffee brewing methods and can accommodate different levels of coffee intensity</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Assorted coffee includes a variety of blends, roasts and flavors. Each type of coffee beverage is made with different coffee brewing methods and can accommodate different levels of coffee intensity. Americano coffee is a shot of espresso mixed with hot water, which creates a smooth flavor. Cappuccino coffee is a shot of espresso mixed with steamed milk and topped with foamed milk for a creamy texture. Latte coffee is a shot of espresso mixed with steamed milk and topped with a thin layer of foam. Espresso is a concentrated coffee beverage made from brewing finely ground coffee using pressurized hot water. Cold brew coffee is made by steeping coarsely ground coffee beans in cold water for an extended period of time. French press coffee is made by steeping coarsely ground coffee beans in hot water with a French press coffee maker. Assorted coffee drinks can be enjoyed hot or cold, sweetened or unsweetened, with an assortment of optional flavorings. </span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/assorted-coffee/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wheat From Organic Farms</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/wheat-from-organic-farms/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/wheat-from-organic-farms/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/wheat-from-organic-farms/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Organic wheat is often more flavorful and nutritious than its non-organic counterpart.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Organic wheat is often more flavorful and nutritious than its non-organic counterpart. Wheat from organic farms is a type of wheat that is grown without the use of synthetic fertilizers, pesticides, or other chemicals. These products are not only healthier for the environment, but they are also often higher in nutrients than their non-organic counterparts. Organic wheat is often milled into flour that is used to make bread, pasta, cakes, and a variety of other baked goods. Choose organic wheats for the health and safety benefits of organic products.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/wheat-from-organic-farms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Diabetic Cookies</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/diabetic-cookies/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/diabetic-cookies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/diabetic-cookies/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Diabetic cookies are a type of cookie that has been specifically formulated to meet the dietary needs of people with diabetes.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Diabetic cookies are a type of cookie that has been specifically formulated to meet the dietary needs of people with diabetes. These cookies contain ingredients that are low in carbohydrates and sugar, as well as other elements that are beneficial for people with diabetes, such as healthy fats and proteins. Our diabetic cookies also contain dietary fiber to help regulate blood sugar levels and improve digestion. Additionally, our diabetic cookies are fortified with vitamins and minerals to help provide essential nutrients for a diabetic diet.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/diabetic-cookies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Organic Face Scrub</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/organic-face-scrub/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/organic-face-scrub/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/organic-face-scrub/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Organic face scrubs are an effective and natural way to exfoliate and cleanse the face, giving it a healthier, smoother and brighter appearance.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Organic face scrubs are an effective and natural way to exfoliate and cleanse the face, giving it a healthier, smoother and brighter appearance. These scrubs may contain a variety of natural ingredients, such as sugar, salt, ground coffee beans, almonds and oats, which provide gentle yet effective exfoliation. They can also include natural oils, such as jojoba, coconut and almond, which are known for their hydrating and nourishing benefits. Our face scrubs also contain natural extracts, such as aloe vera, lavender, chamomile and green tea, which help to soothe, calm and protect the skin. Additionally, our organic face scrubs also include alpha hydroxy acids which help to reduce the appearance of wrinkles and fine lines while also encouraging healthy cell renewal.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/organic-face-scrub/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cashew Butter</title>
		<link>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/cashew-butter/</link>
					<comments>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/cashew-butter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[petermai6655]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/cashew-butter/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span data-tt="{&#34;paragraphStyle&#34;:{&#34;alignment&#34;:4,&#34;writingDirection&#34;:1}}">Cashew butter is a good source of protein, fiber, healthy fats, and several vitamins and minerals. It is especially high in magnesium and zinc, and is often rich in plant-based iron.</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-tt="{&quot;paragraphStyle&quot;:{&quot;alignment&quot;:4,&quot;writingDirection&quot;:1}}">Cashew butter is a delicious and versatile spread made from ground cashew nuts. It is light and creamy in texture. Cashew butter is a nutritious alternative to other nut butters and can be used in a wide range of recipes. Cashew butter is a good source of protein, fiber, healthy fats, and several vitamins and minerals. It is especially high in magnesium and zinc, and is often rich in plant-based iron. Additionally, it is naturally free from gluten, dairy, and cholesterol. Cashew butter can be used in many different ways. It can be added to smoothies, baked goods, and salad dressings for a creamy texture and nutty flavor. It can also be used to make vegan cheese sauces, as a dip for vegetables or crackers, or as a spread for toast and sandwiches. Many people also enjoy eating it plain, either with a spoon or as a topping for oatmeal and yogurt.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://petermai6655.github.io/MatGauThanKy/product/cashew-butter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
